[MUSIC]
Welcome to Stock from the family.  Today we will talk
about ICICI Principal Life Insurance Company.
So if you have a long
term investment in this or
someone is going to do so now, then this video can be
very important for him.  So let's
cover some stock levels, support, resistance etc. in this video.  We will
analyze it in weekly time frame.
[MUSIC]
is kind of a trade line.  The
stock is seen sustaining above that.
You can see [music] whenever it has
sustained above the trend line, there has been a kind of
pullback.   The
stock has an all-time high of Rs 795.  From there,
a decline was visible.  But again
a kind of pullback was seen on the trend line from here.
One level is 665.  It was
seen sustaining till there and
again a kind of decline was seen from there.
And again a kind of morning
star was seen forming on the trade line and a kind
of pullback was seen.  So traders, if
you have a long term
investment in this, then I will give you some levels.
You can hold it there until it is there.   There
is a level of 665.  Above that, if it
sustains [music] and a kind of
hammer or morning star candle is shown here,
then we can see the stock sustaining till 700.
And if it breaks this level
we can see the stock sustaining till [music]
795.
So if you already have an investment in it,
you can hold it until 795 [MUSIC].
Looking at the negative movement
[Music]
if a negative candle is shown from this level
then we can
see the stock sustaining till ₹60 [Music].
So if anyone wants to make a new investment, then
you can make a new investment up to ₹60.
Please let me know how you liked the video in the comment box.  If you like the video then
like the video and subscribe to the channel.
See you in the next video.
Bye-bye till then.